drop.com 2019-12-13

# Privacy Policy | Drop (formerly Massdrop)

## 1\. OUR APPROACH TO PRIVACY

1.1 Massdrop, Inc. (" **Drop** ", " **we** ", " **our** ", or " **us** ") is strongly committed to protecting and respecting your privacy. This privacy policy sets out how we collect, store, process, transfer, share and use data that identifies or is associated with you (" **personal information** ") and information regarding our use of cookies and similar technologies.

1.2 Drop operates a community-driven e-commerce platform that allows users to discuss, request and receive updates about specific products and features, and for members to market and sell products requested through the platform, in each case using our website at [drop.com](https://drop.com/) (the " **Service** ").

1.3 This privacy policy applies to our Service. Terms used in this privacy policy have the same meaning as in our Terms of Service, unless otherwise defined in this privacy policy.

1.4 Before accessing or using our Service, please ensure that you have read and understood our collection, storage, use and disclosure of your personal information as described in this privacy policy.

1.5 Drop is the data controller of the personal information we hold about you.

## 2\. PERSONAL INFORMATION WE COLLECT ABOUT YOU AND HOW WE USE IT

_Personal information we collect from you directly_

2.1 We collect personal information that you voluntarily submit directly to us when you use our Service. This can include information you provide to us when you register for an account and user profile, fill in a form on our Service, create or edit your user profile on the Service, correspond with us by phone, e-mail or otherwise, subscribe to our mailing lists, newsletters or other forms of marketing communications, respond to a survey, post comments in forums, enter a promotion, or use some other feature of our Service. We may also collect personal information from third parties, such as social networks.

2.2 We will indicate to you where the provision of certain personal information is required in order for us to provide you certain features of the Service. If you choose not to provide such personal information, we may not be able to provide the Service to you or respond to your other requests.

2.3 The list below sets out the categories of personal information we collect about you and how we use that information:

**Contact and profile information.** Personal information, such as your name, username, phone number, address, e-mail address, profile picture and personal information contained in your bio.

**Comments, chat and opinions.** When you contact us directly, e.g. by email, phone or when you complete an online form or participate in an online forum or chat, we will record your comments and opinions.

**Payment and transaction information.** Information such as items purchased, date and time of your transaction, and payment information, such as your credit card or bank account details.

**Preferences.** Preferences set for notifications, marketing communications, how our website is displayed and how you use the Service.

2.4 We may use this information to:

> (a) allow you to log in to and use certain features of the Service, create a profile for you on the Service, and to operate, maintain and provide to you the features of the Service;
> 
> (b) facilitate the shipment of products ordered through the Service;
> 
> (c) communicate with you including sending service-related communications (such as statements, invoices and solicited marketing communications) and unsolicited marketing communications in accordance with your preferences;
> 
> (d) provide customer support and deal with enquiries and complaints made by or about you relating to the Service;
> 
> (e) inform our advertising and marketing, and the development of new products and features available through our Service, or to otherwise monitor and improve our Service; and
> 
> (f) detect and prevent fraud.

2.5 The processing of the above personal information is necessary for:

> (a) the performance of a contract with you and to take steps prior to entering into a contract; and
> 
> (b) our legitimate interests, namely administering, tailoring and improving the Service, informing our direct marketing, communicating with users.

_Personal information we collect from third parties_

2.6 From time to time, we may receive information about you from third parties and other users:

**Information obtained from third parties.** We may obtain information from third parties to enhance or supplement our existing user information. We may also collect information about you that is publicly available. We may combine this information with the information we collect from you directly. For example, we may obtain information when you log in through a third-party social network or authentication service, such as Facebook or Google.

**Information provided by social networks you connect to our Service.** If you connect a social network, such as Facebook, to our Service we will collect personal information from the social network in accordance with your privacy settings on that social network. These services will authenticate your identity and provide you the option to share certain personal information with us, which could include your name, email address, address book and contacts, or other information.

Similarly, when you interact with us through a social media site or third-party service, such as when you like, follow, or share our content on Facebook, Twitter, Pinterest, Instagram, or other sites, we may receive information from the social network, including your profile information, picture, user ID associated with your social media account, and any other information you permit the social network to share with third parties.

The data we receive is dependent on your privacy settings with the social network. You should always review and, if necessary, adjust your privacy settings on third-party websites and services before linking or connecting them to our website or Service.

2.7 We may use this information to:

> (a) authenticate your identity, allow you to access and use certain features of the Service and to create a public profile for you; and
> 
> (b) inform our advertising and marketing, and the development of new products and features available through our Service, or to otherwise monitor and improve our Service.

2.8 If you permit the third-party social network to share your friends list or address book with us, we may use this information to let you know what your friends are doing on our Service and to let your friends know what you are doing on the Service.

2.9 The processing of personal information we collect about you from third parties is necessary for:

> (a) the performance of a contract and taking steps prior to entering into a contract;
> 
> (b) our legitimate interests, namely to tailor our Service to the user and to inform our marketing and product development.

_Personal information we collect about you automatically_

2.10 We also automatically collect personal information indirectly about how you access and use the Service and information about the device you use to access the Service. The list below sets out the categories of personal information we collect about you automatically and how we use that information:

**Information about how you access and use the Service.** For example, the website from which you came and the website to which you are going when you leave our website, how frequently you access the Service, the time you access our Service and how long you use it for, the approximate location that you access the Service from, whether you access the Service from multiple devices, and other actions you take on the Service.

**Information about your device.** We also collect information about the computer, tablet, smartphone or other electronic device you use to connect to our Service. This information can include details about the type of device, unique device identifying numbers, operating systems, browsers and applications connected to our Service through the device, your Internet service provider or mobile network, your IP address and your device’s telephone number (if it has one).

2.11 We may use the information we collect automatically to present the Service to you on your device and to determine products and services that may be of interest to you for marketing purposes. We may also use the personal information we collect from you to monitor and improve the Service and business, and to help us to develop new products and services.

2.12 The processing of the personal information we collect from you automatically is necessary for our legitimate interests, namely: to tailor the Service to the user and to improve the Service generally; to monitor and resolve issues; for marketing purposes; to communicate with users; to contact users; and for the detection and prevention of fraud.

_All personal information_

2.13 We may link or combine the personal information we collect about you and the information we collect automatically. This allows us to provide you with a personalised experience regardless of how you interact with us.

2.14 We may anonymise and aggregate any of the personal information we collect (so that it does not directly identify you). We may use anonymised information for purposes that include testing our IT systems, research, data analysis, improving our Service and developing new products and features. We may also share such anonymised information with others.

2.15 The processing of personal information in this way is necessary for our legitimate interests, namely to monitor and improve our Service.

## 3\. RECIPIENTS OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION

3.1 As required in accordance with how we use it, in addition to the recipients identified in Annex 1 and Annex 2 we may share your personal information with the following parties:

> (a) **Merchants.** When you purchase products offered by third parties through our Service, your personal information may be disclosed to such third parties in order to process and fulfil your order.
> 
> (b) **The community.** When you post user content on our Service, such as your profile information, questions or comments, this content will be visible to other users of our Service.
> 
> (c) **Service providers and advisors.** Third party vendors and other service providers that perform services for us or on our behalf, which may include shipping and logistics services, identifying and serving targeted advertisements, providing mailing, email or chat services, tax and accounting services, payments processing, data enhancement services, fraud prevention, web hosting, or providing analytic services.
> 
> (d) **Select third parties.** We may share your personal information with third parties to the extent you have asked or authorised us to do so, such as the social network you connect to our Service or other parties from which you wish to receive information and marketing messages about products or services that may interest you.
> 
> (e) **Purchasers and third parties in connection with a business transaction.** Personal information may be disclosed to third parties in connection with a transaction, such as a merger, sale of assets or shares, reorganisation, financing, change of control or acquisition of all or a portion of our business.
> 
> (f) **Law enforcement, regulators and other parties for legal reasons.** Third parties as required by law or if we reasonably believe that such action is necessary to (a) comply with the law and the reasonable requests of law enforcement; (b) enforce our Terms of Service or to protect the security or integrity of our Service; and/or (c) exercise or protect the rights, property, or personal safety of Drop, our users or others.

## 4\. MARKETING COMMUNICATIONS

4.1 Our Service is a community where users can discuss and discover new products or features and receive updates and offers on products. We will provide you with updates about the products you have requested or in which you have shown an interest in accordance with the functionality of our Service. To do this, we will use the personal information we collect about you to send you information and updates about products you have requested or in which you have shown an interest on our Service. Most messages we send will be by email.

4.2 If you are in the European Economic Area (" **EEA** "), we will only send you marketing messages if you have given us your consent to do so. If you do not want to receive messages from us, you will be able to tell us by selecting certain boxes on forms we use when we first collect your contact details or by refusing or withdrawing your consent.

4.3 You can change your preferences about the notifications you receive by clicking the unsubscribe link at the bottom of our emails or logging into your account on our website and changing your preferences, although this will not unsubscribe you from administrative emails from us.

## 5\. STORING AND TRANSFERRING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION

5.1 **Retention periods.** We will store payment and transaction information for up to 6 years from the date of your purchase. For all other categories of personal data, we will store it for no longer than necessary for the purposes set out above and in accordance with our legal obligations and legitimate business interests.

5.2 **Security.** We implement appropriate technical and organisational measures to protect your personal information against accidental or unlawful destruction, loss, change or damage. All personal information we collect will be stored on our secure servers, and all transfers of personal information will be protected by TLS encryption technology. We will never send you unsolicited emails or contact you by phone requesting your account ID, password, credit or debit card information or national identification numbers.

5.3 **International Transfers of your Personal Information.** As we are located in the USA, any information you provide will initially be collected and stored in the USA. If you are in the EU or EEA, this may mean that your personal information will be stored in a jurisdiction that offers a level of protection that may, in certain instances, be less protective of your personal information than the jurisdiction you are typically resident in.

5.4 We will take reasonable steps to ensure that your personal information is treated securely and in accordance with applicable law and this privacy policy.

5.5 **Privacy Shield.** We comply with the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield framework and Swiss-U.S. Privacy Shield framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use and retention of personal information received from European Union countries and Switzerland (the " **Privacy Shield** "). We have certified that we adhere to the Privacy Principles of notice, choice, accountability for onward transfer, security, data integrity, purpose limitation, access, and recourse, enforcement and liability (" **Principles** "). If there is any conflict between the policies in this policy and the Principles, the Principles shall govern. To learn more about Privacy Shield, please visit the U.S. Department of Commerce Privacy Shield website: <https://www.privacyshield.gov/>. For more information regarding our Privacy Shield certification, please see our Privacy Shield Privacy Statement addendum.

5.6 If you wish to enquire further about the safeguards we use, please contact us using the details set out at the end of this privacy policy.

## 6\. YOUR RIGHTS IN RESPECT OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION

6.1 In accordance with European Union privacy law, if you are in the EEA you have the following rights in respect of your personal information that we hold:

> (a) **Right of access.** You have the right to obtain:
>
>> (i) confirmation of whether, and where, we are processing your personal information;
>> 
>> (ii) information about the categories of personal information we are processing, the purposes for which we process your personal information and information as to how we determine applicable retention periods;
>> 
>> (iii) information about the categories of recipients with whom we may share your personal information; and
>> 
>> (iv) a copy of the personal information we hold about you.
> 
> (b) **Right of portability.** You have the right, in certain circumstances, to receive a copy of the personal information you have provided to us in a structured, commonly used, machine-readable format that supports re-use, or to request the transfer of your personal data to another person.
> 
> (c) **Right to rectification.** You have the right to obtain rectification of any inaccurate or incomplete personal information we hold about you without undue delay.
> 
> (d) **Right to erasure.** You have the right, in some circumstances, to require us to erase your personal information without undue delay if the continued processing of that personal information is not justified.
> 
> (e) **Right to restriction.** You have the right, in some circumstances, to require us to limit the purposes for which we process your personal information if the continued processing of the personal information in this way is not justified, such as where the accuracy of the personal information is contested by you.
> 
> (f) **Right to object.** You have a right to object to any processing based on our legitimate interests where there are grounds relating to your particular situation. There may be compelling reasons for continuing to process your personal information, and we will assess and inform you if that is the case. You can object to marketing activities for any reason.

6.2 If you wish to exercise one of these rights, please contact us using the contact details at the end of this privacy policy. You may also review and edit the personal information you have submitted to us by logging into your account on our website.

6.3 You also have the right to lodge a complaint to your national data protection authority. Further information about how to contact your local data protection authority is available at <http://ec.europa.eu/justice/data-protection/bodies/authorities/index_en.htm>.

6.4 Residents in other jurisdictions may also have similar rights to the above. Please contact us using the contact details at the end of this privacy policy if you would like to exercise one of these rights, and we will comply with any request to the extent required under applicable law.

## 7\. COOKIES AND SIMILAR TECHNOLOGIES

7.1 Our website uses cookies and similar technologies to distinguish you from other users of our website. This helps us to provide you with a good experience when you browse our website and also allows us to improve our website.

7.2 Cookies are pieces of code that allow for personalisation of our website experience by saving your information such as user ID and other preferences. A cookie is a small data file that we transfer to your computer's hard disk for record-keeping purposes.

7.3 We use the following types of cookies:

> (a) **Strictly necessary cookies.** These are cookies that are required for the operation of our website. They include, for example, cookies that enable you to log into secure areas of our website, use a shopping cart or make use of e-billing services.
> 
> (b) **Analytical/performance cookies.** They allow us to recognise and count the number of visitors and to see how visitors move around our website when they are using it. This helps us to improve the way our website works, for example, by ensuring that users are finding what they are looking for easily. We may use third-party analytics tools such as Google Analytics, to help us measure traffic and usage trends for the Online Services and to understand more about the demographics of our users. You can learn more about Google’s practices at <http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners>, and view its currently available opt-out options at <https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout>.
> 
> (c) **Functionality cookies.** These are used to recognise you when you return to our website. This enables us to personalise our content for you, greet you by name and remember your preferences (for example, your choice of language or region).
> 
> (d) **Targeting cookies.** These cookies record your visit to our website, the pages you have visited and the links you have followed. We will use this information to make our website and the advertising displayed on it, and the marketing messages we send to you more relevant to your interests. We may also share this information with third parties who provide a service to us for this purpose.
> 
> (e) **Third party cookies.** Please be aware that advertisers and other third parties may use their own cookies tags when you click on an advertisement or link on our website. These third parties are responsible for setting out their own cookie and privacy policies.

7.4 The cookies we use are designed to help you get the most from the website but if you do not wish to receive cookies, most browsers allow you to change your cookie settings. Please note that if you choose to refuse cookies you may not be able to use the full functionality of our website. These settings will typically be found in the "options" or "preferences" menu of your browser. In order to understand these settings, the following links may be helpful, otherwise you should use the "Help" option in your browser for more details.

> (a) [Cookie settings in Internet Explorer](https://support.microsoft.com/products/windows)
> 
> (b) [Cookie settings in Firefox](http://support.mozilla.org/kb/cookies)
> 
> (c) [Cookie settings in Chrome](https://support.google.com/chrome/answer/95647?hl=en)
> 
> (d) [Cookie settings in Safari web](https://support.apple.com/kb/PH5042?locale=en_GB) and [iOS](https://support.apple.com/en-gb/HT201265).

7.5 We also use clear gifs in HTML-based emails sent to our Customers to track which emails are opened and which links are clicked by recipients. The information allows for more accurate reporting and improvement of our Service. You can set your e-mail options to prevent the automatic downloading of images that may contain these technologies that would allow us to know whether you have accessed our e-mail and performed certain functions with it.

7.6 If you would like to find out more about cookies and other similar technologies, please visit [www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/) or the Network Advertising Initiative's online sources at [www.networkadvertising.org](http://www.networkadvertising.org/).

7.7 Deleting or blocking cookies may not be effective for all types of tracking technologies, such as Local Storage Objects (LSOs) like Flash objects or HTML5.

7.8 We are unable to respond to Do Not Track signals set by your browser at this time.

## 8\. INTEREST BASED ADVERTISING

8.1 We participate in interest-based advertising and use third party advertising companies to serve you targeted advertisements based on your browsing history. We permit third party online advertising networks, social media companies and other third party services to collect information about your use of our Service over time so that they may play or display ads on our Service, on other websites, apps or services you may use, and on other devices you may use.

8.2 Typically, though not always, the information used for interest-based advertising is collected through cookies or similar tracking technologies. We and our third party partners use this information to make the advertisements you see online more relevant to your interests, as well as to provide advertising-related services such as reporting, attribution, analytics and market research.

8.3 We may also use certain forms of display advertising and other advanced features through Google Universal Analytics, such as Remarketing with Google Analytics, Google Display Network Impression Reporting, the DoubleClick Campaign Manager Integration, and Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting. These features enable us to use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookie) and third-party cookies (such as the Doubleclick advertising cookie) or other third party cookies together to inform, optimise, and display ads based on your past visits to the Service. You may control your advertising preferences or opt-out of certain Google advertising products by visiting the Google Ads Preferences Manager, currently available at <https://google.com/ads/preferences> or by vising NAI’s online resources at <http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices>.

8.4 To learn about interest-based advertising and how you may be able to opt-out of some of this advertising, you may wish to visit:

> (a) the Network Advertising Initiative’s online resources, at <http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices>;
> 
> (b) the DAA’s resources at [www.aboutads.info/choices](http://www.aboutads.info/choices); and/or
> 
> (c) Your Online Choices at [www.youronlinechoices.com/uk](http://www.youronlinechoices.com/uk).

Please note that opting-out of receiving interest-based advertising through the NAI’s and DAA’s or Your Online Choices online resources will only opt-out a user from receiving interest-based ads on that specific browser or device, but the user may still receive interest-based ads on his or her other devices. You must perform the opt-out on each browser or device you use.

8.5 Some of these opt-outs may not be effective unless your browser is set to accept cookies. If you delete cookies, change your browser settings, switch browsers or computers, or use another operating system, you will need to opt-out again.

## 9\. LINKS TO THIRD PARTY SITES

Our Service may, from time to time, contain links to and from third party websites, including those of other users, our partner networks, advertisers, partner merchants, news publications, retailers and affiliates. If you follow a link to any of these websites, please note that these websites have their own privacy policies and that we do not accept any responsibility or liability for their policies. Please check the individual policies before you submit any information to those websites.

## 10\. OUR POLICY TOWARDS CHILDREN

10.1 Our Service is not directed at persons under 13 and we do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13. If you become aware that your child has provided us with personal information, without your consent, then please contact us using the details below so that we can take steps to remove such information and terminate any account your child has created with us.

## 11\. CHANGES TO THIS POLICY

We may update this privacy policy from time to time and so you should review this page periodically. When we change this privacy policy in a material way, we will update the "last modified" date at the end of this privacy policy. Changes to this privacy policy are effective when they are posted on this page.

## 12\. NOTICE TO YOU

If we need to provide you with information about something, whether for legal, marketing or other business related purposes, we will select what we believe is the best way to get in contact with you. We will usually do this through email or by placing a notice on our Service. The fact that we may send notices to you will not stop you from being able to opt out of certain types of contact as described in this privacy policy.

13.1 If you are in the EEA, our representative is Massdrop Ltd. Regardless of your location, please contact [Drop Support](https://drop.com/support) if you have any questions, comments and requests regarding this Privacy Policy.

13.2 This privacy policy was last modified on August 15th, 2018.

### Drop Privacy Shield Statement For EU and Swiss Personal Data Transferred to the US

Drop complies with the EU-US Privacy Shield Framework and the Swiss-US Privacy Shield Framework as set forth by the US Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information from European Union member countries and Switzerland transferred to the United States pursuant to Privacy Shield. Drop has certified that it adheres to the Privacy Shield Principles with respect to such data. If there is any conflict between the policies in this privacy policy and data subject rights under the Privacy Shield Principles, the Privacy Shield Principles shall govern.

To learn more about the Privacy Shield program, and to view our certification page, please visit <https://www.privacyshield.gov/>.

#### Purpose

The purpose of this Drop Privacy Shield Statement (“ **Statement** ”) is to outline how we comply with the Principles with respect to the EU and Swiss personal information we collect and subsequently transfer into the United States. If you would like to obtain additional information regarding our privacy practices in connection with information collected on this website in general, please refer to our Privacy Policy. If there is any conflict between this Statement and the Privacy Policy, this Statement shall prevail.

### Scope

This Statement applies to any personal information received by Drop from the European Union or Switzerland in reliance on Privacy Shield.

### Drop Data Processing Activities

Drop at times acts as a data controller when processing personal data transferred from the EEA or Switzerland. Though the types of data Drop collects and processes may vary depending on the Terms of Service and our customers’ preferences, data we collect typically includes personal information relating to contact information, transaction and purchase history information, web browsing behavior and other information relating to a user’s device used to access the services, and other information as described in our Privacy Policy. Drop processes this data to provide our business and consumer services; customer service and product support; communications and marketing; online advertising; analytics to inform and improve our services; and for other internal purposes.

### Principles

  1. **Notice.** We will provide individuals with notice of our data collection and processing practices in our Privacy Policy, describing what personal information we collect, the purpose and use of personal information, the categories of third parties with whom we may share such information (and the purposes for which we do so), the individual’s right to access such information, the choices and means through which the individual may limit the use and disclosure of personal information, and other disclosures consistent with the Notice Principle.

You can read about our data collection and processing practices in our main Privacy Policy.

  2. **Choice.** We will provide an individual opt-out or opt-in choice before we share their data with third parties other than our agents and service providers, or before we use it for a purpose other than it was originally collected or subsequently authorized. Please note that data sharing only takes place after an active opt-in using functionality within the Service. To limit the use and disclosure of your personal information, please submit a written request to Drop Support.

  3. **Onward Transfers (Transfer to Third Parties).** Drop may transfer personal information to certain third parties (as described in our Privacy Policy). Where we transfer personal information to a third party, will take reasonable and appropriate steps to ensure the third-party processes personal information for limited and specified purposes and in a manner consistent with Drop’s Privacy Shield obligations. Where the transfer is to a third-party agent acting on our behalf, Drop may be liable if such third parties fail to meet those obligations, and we are responsible for the event giving rise to the damage.

  4. **Security.** We take reasonable and appropriate measures to protect personal information from loss, misuse and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration and destruction. We have implemented appropriate physical, electronic and managerial procedures to help safeguard and secure personal information from loss, misuse, unauthorized access or disclosure, alteration or destruction.

  5. **Data Integrity and Purpose Limitation.** We will process personal information in a manner that is compatible with and relevant to the purpose for which it was collected or authorized by individuals. To the extent necessary for those purposes, we will take reasonable steps to ensure that personal information is accurate, complete, current and reliable for its intended use.

  6. **Access.** EU and Swiss individuals have the right to reasonable access to the personal information about you that we hold. On request, we will also take reasonable steps to correct, update, amend or delete any information that is demonstrated to be inaccurate, except where the burden or expense of doing so would be disproportionate to the risks to your privacy in the case in question or where the rights of third parties would be violated.

An individual who seeks access, or who seeks to correct, amend, or delete inaccurate data, should direct their query to [Drop Support](https://drop.com/support). If requested to remove data, we will respond within a reasonable timeframe.

  7. **Jurisdiction and Enforcement.** As part of our participation in Privacy Shield, we are subject to the investigatory and enforcement powers of the US Federal Trade Commission.

  8. **Lawful Requests.** Drop may be required to disclose personal information in response to lawful requests by public authorities, including to meet national security or law enforcement requirements.

  9. **Contact Drop and Recourse**

In compliance with the Privacy Shield Principles, Drop commits to resolve complaints about your privacy and our collection or use of your personal information transferred to the United States pursuant to Privacy Shield. If you have any questions about this Statement or the information that we collect from you in reliance on Privacy Shield, please contact us at [Drop Support](https://drop.com/support).

In the event that you are concerned about how personal information you have provided to Drop has been used, please address your inquiry or complaint first to us at the address listed above. Drop takes all concerns about privacy and use of personal information very seriously, and shall endeavor to reply to you within 45 days of receiving a complaint.

If we fail to respond within that time, or if our response does not adequately address your concerns, you may submit your complaint free of charge to JAMS, Airtime’s designated Privacy Shield dispute resolution provider, using this link: <https://www.jamsadr.com/file-an-eu-us-privacy-shield-or-safe-harbor-claim>.

If your Privacy Shield complaint cannot be resolved through the above channels, under certain conditions, you may invoke binding arbitration for some residual claims not resolved by other redress mechanisms. See Privacy Shield Annex 1 at <https://www.privacyshield.gov/article?id=ANNEX-I-introduction>.

**Last Updated:** August 15th, 2018
